What did you remember
Someone else telling you not to sleep
It was you
Hospital records show I signed it
Handwriting proves I accompanied
an injured boy that day
But whether you're that boy
needs further background verification
I won't jump to conclusions
Sister, since you knew all along
why didn't you say so earlier
Were you waiting to make
Mr Fu feel indebted to you
If I wanted him to feel indebted
I would have said it all at the wedding
Or when the Fus came to me
When you took the keepsake
I could have easily said it
But I didn't
Because I know
gratitude is not a bargaining chip
I know, I know you
didn't use it against me
Based on current evidence
you are not the one who
signed at the hospital back then
You said front door
records show side door
You said ER
but it was night surgery clinic
You said thank you
records say don't leave